Sometimes a collection of data might be considered
pi I while the distinct data elements,
each by itself would not,
for example,
a date of birth alone can be shared by many individuals and is not considered pi I.
However, when combined with a name or other piece of information,
it would significantly narrow the possibility
of association with more individuals.
Cyber security professionals take on the obligation of protecting
many kinds of organizational data and personal information.
We all have PI I and it needs to be protected.
The three elements of the CIA triad play out in our everyday lives.
The next time you go to your physician,
open your email or check the balance of your checking account.
Think about how the people who are entrusted to protect it,
accomplish this responsibility.
It is a different way of thinking and one you
will develop as you progress in your cybersecurity career.